Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities collection, 1962-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Central Business Districts, 1960-1989; (11.5 boxes)
  - Downtown action planning process and program: executive summary, 1988 (Box 5, Volume 11)
    Louisville Central Area, Inc.
  - Downtown Area Redevelopment Plan: Building Envelope Testing, ca. 1981 (Box 5, Volume 12)
    City of Edmonton Planning Department
  - Downtown Area Redevelopment Plan: Downtown Land Use Controls, ca. 1981 (Box 5, Volume 13)
  - Downtown Area Redevelopment Plan: Plan for Public Development, ca. 1981 (Box 5, Volume 14)
  - Downtown building survey, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1977 (Box 5, Volume 15)
  - Downtown council progress report, 1984 (Box 6, Volume 1)
    Anthony M. Caruso
  - Downtown D.C. Recommendations for the Downtown Plan, 1982 (Box 6, Volume 2)
  - Downtown development plan: Louisville, Kentucky, 1989 (Box 6, Volume 3)
  - Downtown development strategy: a progress report, 1979 (Box 6, Volume 4)
    Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Department of City Planning
  - Downtown district action guide, 1979 (Box 6, Volume 5)
    Laurence A. Alexander
  - Downtown Idea Book, 1982 (Box 6, Volume 6)
    Carla J. Robinson
  - Downtown Los Angeles from the Los Angeles times, 1982 (Box 6, Volume 7)
  - Downtown Los Angeles, California: recommendations to strengthen retail activity in downtown Los Angeles, 1978 (Box 6, Volume 8)
    Urban Land Institute
  - Downtown Louisville existing conditions maps: Louisville downtown development plan, 1989 (Box 6, Volume 9)
  - Downtown management: a new role for the private sector, 1983 (Box 6, Volume 10)
    Project for Public Spaces
  - Downtown plan: proposal for citizen review, 1983 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    San Francisco, California Department of City Planning
  - Downtown planning and development annual, 1977 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Laurence A. Alexander, editor
  - Downtown planning issues, 1981 (Box 6, Volume 13)
  - Downtown redevelopment research, 1981 (Box 6, Volume 14)
    Lu Weiming
  - Downtown retail development: conditions for success and project profiles, 1983 (Box 6, Volume 15)
  - Downtown retail development: conditions for success and project profiles: [selections], 1983 (Box 6, Volume 16)
  - Downtown Retail Development Conference, April 14-16, 1983, Washington Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C.: program (Box 6, Volume 17)
    Downtown Retail Development Conference (1983)
  - Downtown revitalization: a compendium of state activities, 1980 (Box 6, Volume 18)
    Council of State Community Affairs Agencies
  - Downtown revitalization in smaller communities: the Casa Grande approach: reviewing a process of implementation, 1983 (Box 6, Volume 19)
    David Devine
  - Downtown zoning concepts: working paper, 1982 (Box 6, Volume 20)
  - Eastern sector [of] Pennsylvania Avenue, undated (Box 6, Volume 21)
  - Economic development resource manual, 1988-1989: City of Elkhart, Indiana (Box 6, Volume 22)
  - Eight Mile Road corridor study, Southfield, Michigan, 1982 (Box 7, Volume 1)
    Christopher Wzacny and Associates
  - Enterprise Democracy Act: summary: bill offered by Gary Hart, 1982 (Box 7, Volume 2)
  - Enterprise zones: assessing their impact on minorities, 1981 (Box 7, Volume 3)
    Margaret Bush Wilson,
  - Enterprise zones: Congress prepares to debate the issues, 1981 (Box 7, Volume 4)
    Joseph Burstein
  - Enterprise zones: pioneering in the inner city, 1980 (Box 7, Volume 5)
    Stuart M. Butler
  - Enterprise zones: tool of urban revitalization, 1981 (Box 7, Volume 6)
    Jon A. Stewart
  - Establishment of Pathmark Supermarket in Bedford Stuyvesant, New York: case history, 1979 (Box 7, Volume 7)
  - Faces and places, 1977 (Box 7, Volume 8)
  - Federal Hill: A Disposition of City-Owned Porperties in Federal Hill, undated (Box 7, Volume 9)
  - Fordham Road: a commercial street revitalization: functional analysis, 1980 (Box 7, Volume 10)
  - Futures for a declining city: a simulation of alternative scenarios for the Cleveland metropolitan area, 1980 (Box 7, Volume 11)
    Katharine L. Bradbury
  - Gananda, New York, 1973 (Box 7, Volume 12)
    Philip A. Kemp
  - Gelebte Stadt = The city lived, 1982 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Senator fur Bau- und Wohnungswesen, Berlin
  - Giving development a push in Snow Hill: how one small city uses a local development corporation, 1980 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Janet Garrett
  - Goals for New Haven, Inc., ca. 1978 (Box 7, Volume 15)
  - Greenmarket: the rebirth of farmers markets in New York City, ca. 1976 (Box 7, Volume 16)
    Barry Benepe
  - Guiding downtown development, 1981 (Box 7, Volume 17)
  - Hartford Retail Core Development Project, 1983 (Box 7, Volume 18)
    Downtown Council of Hartford
  - Harvard Square commercial district: urban design guidelines for the future, 1977 (Box 8, Volume 1)
    Brad Hokanson
  - Hawkins Point/Marley Neck: development opportunities in the Port of Baltimore. Executive summary, 1981 (Box 8, Volume 2)
    Regional Planning Council (Baltimore, Maryland)
  - Hawkins Point/Marley Neck: development opportunities in the Port of Baltimore. Final report, 1981 (Box 8, Volume 3)
  - Home towns come back: how architects are helping rebuild a way of living in our smaller cities and towns, Corning, New York, 1976 (Box 8, Volume 4)
    Geddes Brecher Qualls Cunningham, Architects
  - Houston, Texas metropolitan area ... today: ULI 1982 fall meeting project brochure (Box 8, Volume 5)
  - Houston, district map (Box 8, Volume 6)
  - How people use downtown: pedestrian behavior from People and downtown: use, attitudes, settings, undated (Box 8, Volume 7)
    Arthur L. Grey
  - How to make a mall work for your downtown, undated (Box 8, Volume 8)
  - How to make midtown livable, 1981 (Box 8, Volume 9)
    William H. Whyte
  - How to raise dollars for redevelopment: financing commercial revitalization, 1979 (Box 8, Volume 10)
    Stephen Serchuk
  - If you want to be a customer at a farmers' market, start one, 1976 (Box 8, Volume 11)
    Harriet Friedlander
  - Image of the city, 1960 (Box 8, Volume 12)
    Kevin Lynch
  - In-city new town stalled by environmentalists, 1974 (Box 8, Volume 13)
    James Bailey
  - Indianapolis Regional Center General Plan, 1981 (Box 8, Volume 14)
    Department of Metropolitan Development
  - Infill development strategies, 1982 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Real Estate Research Corporation
  - Inner city markets, USA - Covent Garden Market, London: comparative study, 1977 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Renata Von Tscharner
  - Island Plan, 1984: Brief and Programme (Box 8, Volume 17)
    States of Jersey Island Development Committee
  - It pays to revitalize, 1981 (Box 8, Volume 18)
    David Jones
  - Joliet, IL: city of stone and steel, 1984 (Box 8, Volume 19)
  - Lake Erie, 1983 (Box 8, Volume 20)
  - Landscaping commercial areas: a guide for businesses and community groups, 1978 (Box 8, Volume 21)
  - Last place in the downtown plan: Portland, Oregon, 1983 (Box 8, Volume 22)
  - Liberty State Park, New Jersey: an evaluation of development potential in and around the Liberty State Park site, 1977 (Box 8, Volume 23)
  - Living downtown: a recommendation by the American Institute of Architects R/UDAT Team for Downtown Living in Seattle, 1981 (Box 8, Volume 24)
  - Living downtown for Washington, D.C.: planning concepts, 1981 (Box 9, Volume 1)
    District of Columbia Office of Planning and Development
  - Living downtown for Washington, D.C.: resolving problems and opportunities, 1982 (Box 9, Volume 2)
    Wallace, Roberts and Todd
  - Living downtown for Washington, D.C.: A Summary, 1981 (Box 9, Volume 3)
  - Living in Boston: a guide to Boston and neighborhoods for people interested in city living, 1978 (Box 9, Volume 4)
  - Local capital improvements and development management literature synthesis, 1977 (Box 9, Volume 5)
    American Society of Planning Officials
  - Los Angeles central city community plan, 1979 (Box 9, Volume 6)
  - Main street, Ohio: opportunities for bringing people back downtown, 1981 (Box 9, Volume 7)
  - Mainstreet revitalization: program guidelines, undated (Box 9, Volume 8)
    Ontario Ministry of Housing
  - Managing Chicago's urban dollar: based on a colloquium convened by TRUST, Inc., 1976 (Box 9, Volume 9)
    Judith D. Feins
  - Managing design and development downtown, 1982 (Box 9, Volume 10)
    U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development
  - Managing downtown public spaces, 1984 (Box 9, Volume 11)
    Project for Public Spaces, Inc.
  - Market assessment for downtown, Washington, D.C.: executive summary, 1981 (Box 9, Volume 12)
    Tischler, Montasser and Associates
  - Midland Street development area study, Bay City, Michigan. Phase two, Midland Street corridor urban design plan, 1981 (Box 9, Volume 13)
  - Midtown development, 1981 (Box 9, Volume 14)
  - Midtown development project zoning regulations study: final draft, 1980 (Box 9, Volume 15)
    Davis, Brody and Associates
  - Milwaukee Area Urban Strategy: Final Report, 1980 (Box 9, Volume 16)
  - Minneapolis metro center. A Look back, 1969-1977, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 1)
  - Minneapolis metro center. Forecasts to 1990, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 2)
  - Minneapolis metro center. Plan, 1990, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 3)
  - Minneapolis metro center. Planning principles, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 4)
  - Mixed-Use Developments: New Ways of Land Use, 1976 (Box 10, Volume 5)
  - Monitoring report and information appendices for the Bethesda CBD, 1985 (Box 10, Volume 6)
  - Neighborhood commercial rezoning study: proposed zoning framework, 1982 (Box 10, Volume 7)
  - New answer for an old problem: urban jobs and enterprise zones, 1981 (Box 10, Volume 8)
    Richard Cherry
  - New directions for Concord: an analysis of the potential for central business district redevelopment: summary report, ca. 1978 (Box 10, Volume 9)
  - New directions for Urban Main Streets (Box 10, Volume 10)
    Suzanne G. Dane, editor
  - New era, downtown San Diego, ca. 1985 (Box 10, Volume 11)
  - New frontier for business opportunities: a handbook for private iniatiative in community revitalization, undated (Box 10, Volume 12)
  - New Jersey, the ultimate corporate environment, 1986 (Box 10, Volume 13)
  - New village markets, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 14)
    Judith Joy
  - New York and Tokyo: a study in crowding. Part I; Part II, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 15)
  - Newkirk Plaza revitalization, 1976 (Box 10, Volume 16)
  - Nicollet Mall: civic cooperation to preserve downtown's vitality, 1971 (Box 10, Volume 17)
    Frederick T. Aschman
  - No little plans: Fairfax County's PLUS program for managing growth, 1977 (Box 10, Volume 18)
    Grace Dawson
  - North midtown area plan, 1976 (Box 10, Volume 19)
  - On building downtown: design guidelines for the core area, 1974 (2nd ed.) (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Abram, Nowski & McLaughlin, Associates
  - Opportunity Camden, 1987 (Box 10, Volume 21)
  - Options for a unique Texas Place South Main Street area, 1975 (Box 10, Volume 22)
    Rice Center for Community Design and Research
  - Orlando metropolitan area ... today: ULI 1979 fall meeting project brochure (Box 11, Volume 1)
    Carla S. Crane
  - Our Stake in the Urban Condition: Urban Enterprise Zones, 1975 (Box 11, Volume 2)
    Adam Simms
  - Pacific Avenue design plan: a manual of guidelines and programs ... City of Santa Cruz, 1978 (Box 11, Volume 3)
    Charles Hall Page & Associates
  - Parking requirements for shopping centers: summary recommendations, 1981 (Box 11, Volume 4)
    Wilbur Smith and Associates
  - Pennsylvania Avenue plan, 1974, 1975 (Box 11, Volume 5)
    Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation
  - Perspective for the cities, 1982 (Box 11, Volume 6)
    Jan Schaefer
  - Pittsburgh post-gazette. Special edition on downtown redevelopment, November, 1979 (Box 11, Volume 7)
  - Planning for underground space, 1983 (Box 11, Volume 8)
    Raymond L. Sterling,
  - Practical guide to storefront rehabilitation, 1977 (Box 11, Volume 9)
    Norman M. Mintz
  - Project Rise: a proposal for the revitalization and improvement of shopping environments through design: six month progress report, 1979 (Box 11, Volume 10)
    Yonkers, N.Y. Planning Bureau
  - Promoting effectively for downtown business: dynamic new case studies, 1983 (Box 11, Volume 11)
  - Public benefit improvement guidelines, 1976 (Box 11, Volume 12)
    Don Erickson
  - Rebuilding New Orleans: financing public facilities, 1982 (Box 11, Volume 13)
    Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co.
  - Recycling cities, 1973 (Box 11, Volume 14)
  - Regional center plan: Economic Analysis and Development Strategy for Downtown Indianapolis, 1980 (Box 11, Volume 15)
  - Renaissance of Older Industrial Urban Areas (Urban Renaissance in Europe Study Series), 1981 (Box 11, Volume 16)
    Council of Europe
  - Report to the Mayor on the linkage between downtown development and neighborhood housing, 1983 (Box 11, Volume 17)
  - Restoration of confidence: the achievements of the Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1967-1981 (Box 11, Volume 18)
  - Revitalization of the city center, 1987 (Box 11, Volume 19)
    W. Arthur Mehoff
  - Revitalizing downtown Minneapolis: a case study: presented at North Atlantic Treaty Organisation's Committee ... meeting ..., 1980 (Box 11, Volume 20)
    Lawrence M. Irvin
  - Revitalizing downtown retailing: trends and opportunities, 1983 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - Revitalizing main street: small town public policy, 1982 (Box 11, Volume 22)
    Robert Craycroft
  - Revitalizing older business districts can be successful via adherence to a comprehensive, four-point program, 1977 (Box 11, Volume 23)
    John Sower
  - San Diego's Lively New and Old Downtown, 1987 (Box 11, Volume 24)
  - Shared parking, 1983 (Box 12, Volume 1)
    Barton-Aschman Associates
  - Shop front: some thought on the design of shopfronts presented in pictures, undated (Box 12, Volume 2)
  - Shopping center development handbook, 1977 (Box 12, Volume 3)
    J. Ross McKeever
  - Sidewalk cafes, 1977 (Box 12, Volume 4)
  - Six year development program, 1981-1986; Capital budget and community development block grant program: draft for discussion (Box 12, Volume 5)
    Pittsburgh, Pa.
  - South central Los Angeles district plan, 1979 (Box 12, Volume 6)
  - Southeast Los Angeles district proposed plan, 1978 (Box 12, Volume 7)
  - St. Louis: the central west end, undated (Box 12, Volume 8)
    Phyllis Myers
  - Street tree plan for Oakland: prelimary draft submittal, 1979 (Box 12, Volume 9)
    Urban Trees Design Group
  - String of pearls: a master plan for the development of the North Canadian River, Oklahoma City, OK, 1980 (Box 12, Volume 10)
    Planning Development Services
  - Town center zoning ordinance, 1979 (Box 12, Volume 11)
    Rockville, Maryland
  - Urban indicators for city planning of Zurich, ca. 1985 (Box 13, Volume 1)
    Gerhard B. Sidler
  - Urban reinvestment task force progress report, St. Johns business district, Portland, Oregon, 1978 (Box 13, Volume 2)
    Portland, Or. Development Commission
  - Warehouse district: urban design guidelines, 1984 (Box 13, Volume 3)
    Robert Bann
  - Wharf Shopping Mall, the Woodlands, Texas: an evaluation of investment and redevelopment strategies, 1982 (Box 13, Volume 4)
  - What's so special about Navasota?: a townscape preservation and enhancement program for Navasota, Texas, 1980 (Box 13, Volume 5)
  - Where's main street, U.S.A.?, 1984 (Box 13, Volume 6)
    Gail Garfield Schwartz
  - Who will save the American city?: a transcript of the Providence Journal/Brown University Public Affairs Conference, Nov. 30-Dec. 2, 1982 (Box 13, Volume 7)
    Public Affairs Conference (1982: Brown University)
  - Whose town is it anyway?: proceedings of the conference held to review the progress of the European Campaign for Urban Renaissance ..., 1982 (Box 13, Volume 8)
  - Working paper of the center for the study of the city and its environment, 1972 (Box 13, Volume 9)
    Institution for Social Policy Studies
- Series 4: Cultural Facilities, 1966-1989; (3.5 boxes)
  This series contains materials on the municipal funding of public art and the improvement of community cultural facilities such as art centers, concert halls, opera houses, and theaters. The cities covered include Seattle, Rochester, Lowell, Knox, and Washington, D.C.
  - 1894 Grand Opera House and Hotel, Galveston, 1976 (Box 13, Volume 10)
    Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Associates
  - American West. Vol. 3, no. 3 (Summer 1966) (Box 13, Volume 11)
  - Art spaces and economics, 1984 (Box 13, Volume 12)
    Lois Friedland
  - Artists live/work space: changing public policy, 1981 (Box 13, Volume 13)
  - Arts and center-city revitalization: a case study of Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1981 (Box 13, Volume 14)
    Susan Mooring Hollis
  - Arts and urban development: critical comment and discussion, 1980 (Box 13, Volume 15)
    University of Akron. Center for Urban Studies
  - Arts and urban development: four case studies: the Massachusetts State Transportation Building, the Yale Center for British Art..., 1988 (Box 13, Volume 16)
    J. Mark Davidson Schuster,
  - Arts and urban development: urban renaissance brings financial strategies to the arts, 1984 (Box 13, Volume 17)
    Christine Ann Fedukowski
  - Arts and urban planning: new sources of funding: a preliminary outline for study, 1982 (Box 13, Volume 18)
  - Arts at Irving Commons: a proposal and plan, 1982 (Box 13, Volume 19)
    Don S. Anderson
  - Arts in Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 13, Volume 20)
    Loti Falk
  - Arts in the community, Knox, 1983 (Box 13, Volume 21)
  - Arts space: report of the Mayors Blue Ribbon Committee, 1988 (Box 13, Volume 22)
    Tracy Dillard
  - Artwork network: a planning study for Seattle: art in the civic context, 1984 (Box 14, Volume 1)
  - Athena Tacha public works, 1970-1988: a retrospective exhibition, 1989 (Box 14, Volume 2)
    Catherine M. Howett
  - Bricks, mortar and the performing arts, 1975 (Box 14, Volume 3)
    Twentieth Century Fund
  - Bringing people back downtown with a little help from the arts, 1979 (Box 14, Volume 4)
    Jerry Hagstrom
  - Carolina Theatre, Winston-Salem, N.C.: a feasibility study, 1976 (Box 14, Volume 5)
  - City Comparisons of Cultural Rehabilitation Projects, 1981 (Box 14, Volume 6)
  - Comprehensive arts facilities plan for Dallas, 1977 (Box 14, Volume 7)
    Carr, Lynch Associates
  - Cultural and economic development: how do they come together?, undated (Box 14, Volume 8)
    James L. Shanahan
  - Cultural center for New Brunswick: a report of the New Brunswick Arts Development Commission (Box 14, Volume 9)
    Jane Tublin
  - Cultural cooperation: the new frontier, 1983 (Box 14, Volume 10)
    Ralph Burgard
  - Cultural facilities: a catalog of projects, undated (Box 14, Volume 11)
  - Downtown stages: new theatres for Washington, D.C., 1986 (Box 14, Volume 12)
    League of Washington Theatres
  - Economic feasibility study/Folly Theatre restoration, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 (Box 14, Volume 13)
    Midwest Research Institute
  - Escondido Civic Center Master Plan, Vol. 5 - Policy Statement, 1984 (Box 14, Volume 14)
  - Firstside Cultural District: a strategy for revitalization, undated (Box 14, Volume 15)
    Vision, Inc.
  - Glasgow isn't Paris, but ..., 1989 (Box 14, Volume 16)
    Bill Bryson
  - Greater Paterson Arts Council loft survey, 1980 (Box 14, Volume 17)
  - Hagi International Sculpture Symposium: term, September 11, 1981-November 15, 1981: place, Shizuki Nishi Koen, Horiuchi, Hagi City ... (Box 14, Volume 18)
    Hagi International Sculpture Symposium (1981: Hagi, Japan)
  - Hanover arts project: a planned development of artists lofts, studios and shops ... the new center of Washington's arts community, 1981 (Box 14, Volume 19)
    Robert Lennon
  - How cities support the arts, 1981 (Box 14, Volume 20)
    David Cwi
  - How the arts made a difference, 1989 (Box 14, Volume 21)
    Adolfo V. Nodal
  - Howard Theater: intensive architectural survey: D.C. blacks in the arts, 1987 (Box 15, Volume 1)
    Suman Sorg
  - Hudson Mohawk Urban Cultural Park: management plan elements (2 part report), 1984 (Box 15, Volume 2)
    Fish Buckhurst
  - Knox, a living and growing city, 1983 (Box 15, Volume 3)
  - Living over the museum: mixed-use cultural projects, 1981 (Box 15, Volume 4)
    Robert A. Peck,
  - Lowell Cultural Plan, 1987-1997 (Box 15, Volume 5)
  - Lowertown artist housing project, 1983 (Box 15, Volume 6)
  - Massachusetts Museum of Contemporary Art, 1989 (Box 15, Volume 7)
  - Minneapolis warehouse artist living/working space project, 1979 (Box 15, Volume 8)
  - Minneapolis warehouse artist living/working space project: Executive Summary, 1979 (Box 15, Volume 9)
  - Minnesota highway project, 1975 (Box 15, Volume 10)
    Andrew Leicester
  - New home for Pittsburgh's performing arts: a major new downtown office development (Box 15, Volume 11)
  - North Loop Theater study: a performing arts center for Chicago, 1980 (Box 15, Volume 12)
    North Loop Theater Management Committee
  - Outdoor sculpture in metro Phoenix, 1986 (1st ed.) (Box 15, Volume 13)
    Jan Booth Sheridan
  - Outlook for Broadway: making sense of the Mayor's Theatre Advisory Council proposals, undated (Box 15, Volume 14)
    Jamie Malanowski
  - Perspectives on the economic development potential of cultural resources, 1978 (Box 15, Volume 15)
    Louise W. Wiener
  - Perspectives on the economic development potential of cultural resources, 1978 (Box 15, Volume 16)
  - Place of the arts in new towns, 1973 (Box 16, Volume 1)
  - Plan for the downtown cultural district, Rochester, New York, 1979 (Box 16, Volume 2)
    Sasaki Associates
  - Playhouse Square development, Cleveland, Ohio, undated (Box 16, Volume 3)
  - Preliminary design scenario: Yerba Buena Center cultural plan, 1981 (Box 16, Volume 4)
    Morrish & Fleissig, Associates
  - Public art redefined by California cities, 1987 (Thesis) (Box 16, Volume 5)
    Sondra Clarke Boliek
  - Public spaces and places for arts, 1986 (Box 16, Volume 6)
  - Report and recommendations, 1981 (Box 16, Volume 7)
    Yerba Buena Task Force on Finance
  - Rethinking the performing arts center, 1983 (Box 16, Volume 8)
  - Seattle artists' housing handbook: creating and controlling living/working space through building conversion, 1980 (Box 16, Volume 9)
    Vivian Kahn
  - Seattle artists' housing handbook: creating and controlling living/working space through building conversion. Appendix, 1980 (Box 16, Volume 10)
  - Special space: a guide to artists's housing and loft living, 1981 (Box 16, Volume 11)
    Wilkie Farr & Gallagher
  - Urban environmental design and the arts, 1979 (Box 16, Volume 12)
    Andrew Euston
  - An Urban Renaissance: role of the arts in inner city regeneration and the case for increased public/private sector cooperation, 1987 (Box 16, Volume 13)
  - YBC cultural planning workbook, ca. 1981 (Box 16, Volume 14)
    San Francisco, California Redevelopment Agency
- Series 5: Design, 1962-1989; (6.5 boxes)
  This series contains various technical, prescriptive, and theoretical materials on urban design, architecture, and landscape architecture. The subjects covered range from studies of classical Greek, Gothic, and twelfth-century Chinese architecture to surveys of contemporary British, German, Italian, and Swedish architecture to manuals on pedestrian design and articles on vandalism deterrence. The cities and regions covered include Berlin, Australia, Calgary, New Orleans, Brooklyn, rural Texas, and Concho, Arizona.
  - Aloha Tower Plaza: development prospectus and request for qualifications, 1983 (Box 17, Volume 1)
  - Architecture: Action and Plan, 1967 (Box 17, Volume 2)
    Peter Cook
  - Architecture evolving: an Illinois saga, 1976 (Box 17, Volume 3)
    William T. Brown